[FromFile]
\\aleut\public\mikeroz\Welcome to the .wav=Welcome to the ACME Movie theater. 
\\aleut\public\mikeroz\Speak the name 1.wav=Speak the name of the movie you want to see, or say, "List Movies" to hear currently playing movies.
\\aleut\public\mikeroz\The following m.wav=The following movies are playing at ACME theaters: Air force one. Conspiracy theory. Contact. George of the jungle. Hoodlum. Masterminds. Men in Black. Mimic. A Smile like Yours. Steel. And, Money Talks.
\\aleut\public\mikeroz\Air Force One s.wav=Air Force One, starring Harrison Ford, is showing at 1:15, 3:30, 6:00, and 9:15. 
\\aleut\public\mikeroz\Do you want to .wav=Do you want to hear about another movie?
\\aleut\public\mikeroz\The ACME theate.wav=The ACME theaters are located on Gilman Blvd., just east of 900. Thank you for calling ACME theater's information service. Goodbye.

[Counts]
1=Welcome to the ACME Movie theater. 
2=Speak the name of the movie you want to see, or say, "List Movies" to hear currently playing movies.
3=<Listening>
3=<Recognized>
1=The following movies are playing at ACME theaters: Air force one. Conspiracy theory. Contact. George of the jungle. Hoodlum. Masterminds. Men in Black. Mimic. A Smile like Yours. Steel. And, Money Talks.
1=Air Force One, starring Harrison Ford, is showing at 1:15, 3:30, 6:00, and 9:15. 
1=Do you want to hear about another movie?
1=The ACME theaters are located on Gilman Blvd., just east of 900. Thank you for calling ACME theater's information service. Goodbye.

[Ignored]
=<Listening>
=<Recognized>

