// This grammar demonstrates the generation of a limited domain
// grammar just by specifying the limited-domain chunks

[Grammar]
langid=1033
type=limited-domain
// You can also set type=dictation to make a dictation grammar

// The following lists acceptable words within the limited domain
// grammar. If the grammar is dictation then the words list
// likely dictation words
[Words]
=hello
=mike
=this
=is
=a
=test
=hellos

// To set one or more topics to be used for dictation (and some
// limited domain grammars), use the following
[Topics]
=E-mail
=Computer

// To specify word groups, have one section listing all of the
// different groups, and words within each group under their
// own section
[WordGroups]
=Cities
=States

[Cities]
=New York
=Seattle
=Buffalo
=Washington D.C.

[States]
=Washington
=California
=Oregon
=New York
=Vermont
