// This grammar demonstrates using speech recognition to switch
// the TV channel. The (Commands) part has a list of channels.
// It demonstrates using the command-style rules, which return
// a command ID. We don't need to enter a [<Start>] becuase
// that defaults to <Start> = [opt] (JunkBegin) (Commands) [opt] (JunkEnd)
// There are even some default JunkBegin and JunkEnd phrases
// we'll use


// Try saying:
//   I want to watch CNN
//   Switch to MSNBC
//   ABC please

[(Commands)]
1=C N N
2=N B C
3=C B S
4=A B C
5=M S N B C
6=[opt] the Discovery [opt] channel
7=Nickelodian
8=A and E

